各位 我有个大好消息要宣布一下
Guys! I have something really exciting to say.
你能不能先闭嘴两个小时
How about you pause your piehole for two hours?
我们待会再聊
We'll get to you later.
我们都洗耳恭听了  丽芙
We're all listening, Liv.
很好
Okay.
今年夏天威斯康星州
There is a major film
有一部大电影要进行拍摄
shooting in Wisconsin this summer,
我被提名参演一个主要角色
and I'm up for a big part.
真刺激  电影讲什么的
How exciting! What's it about?
大概是关于一群狼崽子在太空里的吧
It's based on some book about wolves in space.
《太空狼人》
"Space Werewolves!"
这是我最喜欢的漫画小说了
That is my favorite graphic novel.
不会吧
No way!
他们想让我饰演特里斯坦
They want me to play Tristan.
莫非是特里斯坦·莱肯
As in Tristan Lycanth?
对
Yeah.
那个英雄
The hero?
哈哈  特里斯坦是个男孩
Ha ha, but Tristan's a boy.
准确地说是半狼人半男孩
Technically half-boy, half-werewolf.
但他绝对不会是个女孩子
But he is definitely not a girl.
对  暂时还不是
Right. Not yet.
但是制片人看了我在《放声歌唱》里的表现
But the people making the movie saw my episode of Sing it Loud!
就是我在国际空间站里唱女高音
right where I dreamt that I was on an international space station
打碎了本要撞击地球的小行星
and I saved the earth by singing the high note
拯救了芸芸众生的那一集
that shattered the asteroid before it hit earth. Aah!
我太喜欢那集了
I love that episode.
真的吗 我觉得这里面逻辑错误不少啊
Really? 'Cause I had some logic problems with it.
但是你太出彩了 亲爱的
But you sparkled, honey.
他们实在是太喜欢我了 甚至要考虑把原著的男性角色
They liked it so much that they're considering changing the role of Tristan
为了我而改成女的
into a girl just for me.
我为了丽芙着想  必须要阻止她
I had to stop Liv for her own good.
脑残粉太痴狂了
Fanboys are crazy.
我明白这点  因为我也是其中之一
I should know. I'm one of them.
那可是特里斯坦·莱肯啊
We're talking about Tristan Lycanth.
自由世界的捍卫者啊
Keeper of the claw of freedom.
这俩根本就摆不到一起去
Does this match this?